Rehmus, Charles Arbitration files 6212
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Charles Rehmus Arbitration files
1963-2006
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Rehmus, Charles
6212
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Records.
8258622
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 17, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Rehmus, Charles M.
8258622
- Arbitration Awards 1963-1969 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Arbitration Awards 1963-1969 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Arbitration Awards 1970-1971 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Arbitration Awards 1970-1971 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Arbitration Awards 1972 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Arbitration Awards 1972 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Arbitration Awards 1973 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Arbitration Awards 1973 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Arbitration Awards 1974 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Arbitration Awards 1974 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Arbitration Awards 1975 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Arbitration Awards 1975 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Arbitration Awards 1976 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Arbitration Awards 1976 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Arbitration Awards 1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Arbitration Awards 1978 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Arbitration Awards 1978 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Arbitration Awards 1979 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Arbitration Awards 1979 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Arbitration Awards 1980-1982 (folder 1 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Arbitration Awards 1980-1982 (folder 2 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Arbitration Awards 1980-1982 (folder 3 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Arbitration Awards 1983-1984 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Arbitration Awards 1983-1984 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Arbitration Awards 1985-1987 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Arbitration Awards 1985-1987 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Arbitration Awards 1988-1990 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Arbitration Awards 1988-1990 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 9)
- National Academy of Arbitrators Advisory Opinions (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Arbitration Awards 1991-1993 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Arbitration Awards 1991-1993 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Arbitration Awards 1994-1996 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Arbitration Awards 1994-1996 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Arbitration Awards 1997-1998 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Arbitration Awards 1997-1998 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Arbitration Awards 1999-2000 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Arbitration Awards 1999-2000 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Arbitration Awards 2000-2002 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Arbitration Awards 2000-2002 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Arbitration Awards 2003-2004 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Arbitration Awards 2003-2004 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Arbitration Awards 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- SD Transit Corp. & SD Bus Drivers Union, ATU Local 1309 Arbitration Exhibits (folder 1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 8)
- SD Transit Corp. & SD Bus Drivers Union, ATU Local 1309 Arbitration Exhibits (folder 2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Incoming Correspondences 1956-1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Incoming Correspondences 1980-2006 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Incoming Correspondences 1980-2006 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 12)
- National Academy of Arbitrators Membership Directory, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 13)